<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OptimaAI</string>
    <string name="ask_gemini">Ask Gemini</string>
    <string name="type_your_question">Type Your Question</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="response_from_gemini">Response from gemini</string>
    <string name="image_logo">Image_Logo</string>
    <string name="login">L o g i n</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="login_page">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account_yet_register">Don\'t have an account yet? Register</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account_login">Already have an account? Login</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="text_generation_feature">Text Generation Feature</string>
    <string name="business_consult">Business Consult</string>
    <string name="copywriter">Copywriter</string>
    <string name="idea_generator">Idea Generator</string>
    <string name="this_is_a_user_message">This is a user message</string>
    <string name="this_is_a_bot_response">This is a bot response</string>
    <string name="ask_anything_about_business">Ask anything about business…</string>
    <string name="response_will_appear_here">Response will appear here…</string>
    <string name="send_prompt">Send Prompt</string>
    <string name="ai_response">AI Response</string>
    <string name="Prompt_Suggestions">
    Crafting the perfect prompt is key to unlocking the AI\'s full potential. Here is a comprehensive guide on how to structure your prompts to get the best possible business advice for an MSME.\n\n
    <b>How to Craft the Perfect Prompt for Maximizing Your Business</b>\n\n
    To get high-quality, actionable advice from the AI, your prompt needs to be more than just a simple question. Follow these principles to get maximum output.\n\n
    <b>1. Be Specific and Provide Rich Context</b>\n
    The AI needs details to give a tailored solution. The more context you provide, the less the AI has to guess.\n
    <i>Instead of: "How do I increase sales?"</i>\n
    <i>Try: "I run a small coffee shop in Makassar called \'Kopi Kita\'. My target customers are university students aged 18-25. My sales are high in the morning but very low in the afternoon. What are three creative, low-budget marketing strategies to increase my afternoon sales?"</i>\n\n
    <b>2. Define a Clear Goal and Objective</b>\n
    Tell the AI exactly what you want to achieve with its answer.\n
    <i>Instead of: "Tell me about social media."</i>\n
    <i>Try: "My goal is to gain 500 new, authentic Instagram followers for my handmade jewelry business. The objective is to increase brand awareness and drive traffic to my Shopee store."</i>\n\n
    <b>3. Assign a Persona or Role</b>\n
    This is a powerful technique. Instructing the AI to act as a specific expert frames its knowledge and tone.\n
    <i>Instead of: "What should I post on Instagram?"</i>\n
    <i>Try: "Act as a professional social media marketing consultant specializing in Indonesian fashion brands. You are an expert in visual branding and Gen Z marketing."</i>\n\n
    <b>4. Specify the Output Format</b>\n
    Requesting a specific format makes the information easier to digest and act upon.\n
    <i>Instead of: "Give me some ideas."</i>\n
    <i>Try:</i>\n
    • "Provide the answer in a table format with columns for \'Strategy\', \'Estimated Cost\', \'Effort Level\', and \'Potential Impact\'."\n
    • "Create a step-by-step guide on how to set up my first Facebook Ad campaign."\n
    • "Generate five bullet points summarizing the key advantages of using WhatsApp Business for customer service."\n
    • "Write a sample email to a potential B2B client."\n\n
    <b>5. Use Constraints and Keywords</b>\n
    Guide the AI\'s thinking by providing boundaries and key terms.\n
    <i>Instead of: "How can I improve my packaging?"</i>\n
    <i>Try: "Suggest packaging improvements for my \'Sambal Roa\' product. Constraints: The solution must be eco-friendly, keep the product fresh for at least one month, and the cost per unit must be under Rp 2,000. Keywords: sustainable, premium, local heritage."</i>\n\n
    <b>6. Iterate and Refine (Have a Conversation)</b>\n
    Don\'t expect the perfect answer on the first try. Use the AI\'s first response to ask follow-up questions.\n
    <i>After the AI responds:</i>\n
    • "That\'s a great start. For point number 3, can you elaborate further and give me a specific example for a food and beverage business?"\n
    • "Can you rewrite that social media caption in a more casual and humorous tone?"\n
    • "Which of those three options do you think has the highest ROI (Return on Investment)?"\n\n
    By combining these principles, you move from simple questions to strategic conversations, forcing the AI to provide responses that are not just generic, but genuinely valuable and actionable for your business.
</string>
    <string name="consult">Consult</string>
    <string name="chat_title">Chat Title</string>
    <string name="chat_date">3 Agustus 2025</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="consult_history">Consult History</string>
    <string name="start_new_consult">Start new consult</string>
    <string name="your_question">Your question...</string>
    <string name="set_tone">Set Tone</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="masukkan_gaya_sendiri_fitur_pro">Masukkan gaya sendiri (Fitur Pro)</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="set_rules">Set Rules</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to OptimaAI!</string>
    <string name="login_to_continue">Login to continue</string>
    <string name="logo_apk">logo_apk</string>
    <string name="make_a_new_account">Make a new account</string>
    <string name="business_ai_assistant">Business AI Assistant.</string>
    <string name="i_agree_to_the_terms_amp_conditions"><![CDATA[I agree to the Terms & Conditions]]></string>
    <!-- res/values/strings.xml -->
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_content">
    "Selamat datang di OptimaAI!\n\n"
    "Dengan menggunakan aplikasi ini, Anda setuju untuk terikat oleh Syarat dan Ketentuan berikut. Mohon baca dengan saksama.\n\n"
    "1. Penggunaan Akun\n"
    "Anda bertanggung jawab untuk menjaga kerahasiaan akun dan kata sandi Anda. Semua aktivitas yang terjadi di bawah akun Anda adalah tanggung jawab Anda.\n\n"
    "2. Layanan AI\n"
    "Saran yang diberikan oleh AI bersifat informatif dan tidak boleh dianggap sebagai nasihat profesional (hukum, keuangan, dll.). Keputusan bisnis tetap menjadi tanggung jawab penuh pengguna.\n\n"
    "3. Konten Pengguna\n"
    "Anda memiliki semua data dan konten yang Anda masukkan ke dalam aplikasi. Kami tidak akan menggunakan data Anda untuk tujuan apa pun tanpa persetujuan Anda.\n\n"
    "4. Batasan Tanggung Jawab\n"
    "OptimaAI tidak bertanggung jawab atas kerugian bisnis atau kerusakan apa pun yang timbul dari penggunaan atau ketidakmampuan untuk menggunakan layanan kami.\n\n"
    "5. Perubahan Ketentuan\n"
    "Kami berhak untuk mengubah Syarat dan Ketentuan ini kapan saja. Perubahan akan diinformasikan melalui aplikasi atau email.\n\n"
    "Terima kasih telah menggunakan OptimaAI untuk membantu mengembangkan bisnis Anda."
</string>
</resources>